A song I've never heard before Just kicked down a
forgotten door A tidal wave of pure relief
Moments break from all the grief You're by my
side
In this strange and foreign land But underneath
the happy tears Are all the ghosts of these long
years
I'm trying to find my way back home Through the
static and the chrome The 80s beat is in my soul
But the darkness still has its control A song of
home coming in my head For all the words I haven't
said I'm trying to get back to the light With all
of my remaining might
I
see the plains outside the glass And pray this
fragile feeling's built to last Your quiet
strength, your gentle grace The only safety in
this place But every echo, every sound On this
unholy, hollow ground Pulls me back to that dark
room And the silence of a living tomb
I'm trying to find my way back home Through the
static and the chrome The 80s beat is in my soul
But the darkness still has its control A song of
home coming in my head For all the words I haven't
said I'm trying to get back to the light With all
of my remaining might
Thank you very
much.
♪
Almost home Almost
free
Almost me